Seriously bro I'm going to take it.
It might be the same marketing bitch who gave
birth to the man's presentation was diva
valeu valeu.
Driver needs to think of some idea to sell these Passengers in the bars.
Guy
ти атри ое
You know why you're taking this poison,
right?
I wanted to tell you that otherwise we won't tolerate
this type of behavior here anymore.
That's a lack of glucose in your body.
I'll consult later.
The var asked for a review.
What do you have to control your glucose in your body?
Just take that Passenger Box here and you can continue.
Pix oil
mark the soul of the crazy kid business here two little
box is the pix SPF brigadão tamo together.
Thanks.
Go there or I'll get that one.
You can go there.
Asked for review asked for review.
You have to control your glucose level by a little bit.
Man you're really nervous.
The var said that if you control your glucose level you can stay in the game.
It's just that you take a Passenger's Box
you
not buy.
You turned red.
Calif.
[ [ [ [ [ [ [ [ ] [ [ ] [ [ â .